welcome back to another audacity
欢迎回到另一个大胆的地方
tutorial in this video I'm just going to
这个视频中的教程 我只想
go to the file open
转到打开的文件
we're gonna bring in some audio I'll do
我们会带来一些音频 我会做
this more jazz guitar it's a wav file
这把更爵士乐的吉他是一个wav文件
and I'm going to show you how to use cut
我将向您演示如何使用CUT
copy and paste and move sections of your
复制、粘贴和移动您的
audio around so let's just play this and
所以让我们只播放这段视频
listen to see what we have here so just
听一听 看看我们这里有什么
an audio recording of some acoustic
一段声音的录音
guitar so let's say I really only want I
所以比方说我真的只想要
really like this part if I left click
如果我离开点击 我真的喜欢这个部分
here in stand play from here I really
在这里 从这里开始 我真的
like what it sounds like here but I
就像这里听起来的那样 但我
didn't I don't want this intro part so
我是不是不想听这段开场白
we know we've learned in the past
我们知道我们在过去学到了
tutorial we can left-click and keep our
我们可以左键单击并保留我们的教程
left-click down and select by moving so
左键向下单击 然后选择通过移动方式
we can select this part and just hit the
我们可以选择这一部分 然后点击
Delete key if you want to get rid of it
如果您想要删除密钥 请删除它
but maybe we have some timing issues
但也许我们在时间上有一些问题
it's like part of a video and we want to
这就像是视频的一部分 我们想
keep the timing intact
保持计时不变
I can go edit undo we can actually just
我可以去编辑撤销我们实际上可以
create silence for this part we can
为这一部分创造沉默 我们可以
select the whole thing and if we hover
选择整件事 如果我们悬停
over here this icon says silence audio
在这里 这个图标表示静音音频
selection if we hit this it just creates
选择如果我们点击这个 它就会创建
silence there but it doesn't actually
沉默在那里 但实际上并不是
delete it so if we want to remove a
删除它 以便我们想要删除一个
portion of the audio without actually
音频的一部分 而不实际
cutting out that section just use this
剪掉那一段就用这个
silence tool so we can silence any part
静音工具 我们可以让任何部分静音
of this audio we want to and it creates
我们想要的音频 它创造了
a silent lion and then when we play that
一只沉默的狮子 然后当我们玩它的时候
portion it'll just be silent until it
它只会保持沉默 直到它
gets there so that's how you can keep
到达那里 所以这就是你如何保持
timing intact to get that to come back
时间完好无损 让它回来
we can go edit undo edit undo edit undo
我们可以编辑撤消
you can also have the ctrl Z on the
您也可以将Ctrl Z放在
keyboard to undo we could let's say we
要撤消的键盘我们可以说我们
like this portion we just don't want it
就像我们不想要的这部分
to be at the beginning we want to be at
在我们想要的开始
the end we can select it like it was now
最后我们可以像现在一样选择它
so select all this and then we can go to
选择所有这些选项 然后我们可以转到
kept here the cut icon is right up here
保持在这里 切割图标就在这里
to a pair of scissors we can click cut
对于一把剪刀 我们可以点击剪裁
and now it goes away so it's kind of
现在它消失了 所以它就像是
like delete except that it saves that
与DELETE类似 只是它保存了
section in our clipboard and we can then
在我们的剪贴板中 然后我们可以
paste it so if we want to paste it at
粘贴它 这样如果我们想将它粘贴在
the wherever we want to paste it we can
我们可以在任何我们想粘贴的地方粘贴它
just click it's a font to paste at the
只需单击它是一种要粘贴到
end we left-click get our playhead there
结束我们左键点击获取我们的播放头在那里
or this
或者这个
black wine and then we just go to paste
喝黑酒 然后我们就去糊
which is this icon of the clipboard so
剪贴板的图标是什么？
click paste
单击粘贴
now that section appears here so now if
现在这一节出现在这里 所以如果
we play at the beginning it just starts
我们一开始就打球 它才刚刚开始
like this and then it plays this end
像这样 然后它播放这一端
part at the end we can also play it if
最后的角色我们也可以扮演它 如果
we wanted to play at the beginning and
我们一开始就想打球 然后
at the end we can select it and we can
最后我们可以选择它 我们可以
use the copy so this icon here like two
使用复制 这样这里的图标就像两个
pages looks like kind of like we click
页面看起来有点像我们点击
that and that copies and then we can go
那个和那个复印件 然后我们就可以走了
back to the first and hit paste again
返回到第一个 然后再次点击粘贴
and what paste does you'll notice it
你会注意到什么浆糊？
actually just sort of like makes a cut
实际上就像是在做一个切分
and then inserts it in there
然后把它插入到那里
it's not going to paste overtop of any
它不会粘贴在任何
of the audio ahead of it unless we
它前面的音频 除非我们
wanted it to if we want to replace let's
如果我们想要取代它 让我们
say we want to replace this section of
假设我们想要替换这一部分
audio with this clip we just select that
这个剪辑的音频 我们只需选择
portion that we want to replace and then
我们要替换的部分 然后
we well I do so I just want to show that
我们 我是这么做的 所以我只是想展示一下
we still have this in our clipboard
我们的剪贴板上还放着这个
because when we copy we can paste
因为当我们复制时 我们可以粘贴
multiple times let's copy it again and
让我们再复制一次 然后
let you so we know that we have it in
告诉你 让我们知道我们已经成功了
our clipboard and now we can select this
我们的剪贴板 现在我们可以选择这个
and go paste and it will replace this
然后去粘贴 它就会取代这个
portion oops I hit copy instead ctrl C
我按下了复制 而不是按了Ctrl C
also does that and then we come over
也这样做 然后我们就过来
here we can hit control V or just the
在这里 我们可以按下Control V键或只按
paste icon and that will change what was
粘贴图标 这将改变以前的情况
there to this sound here and now it
这就是此时此刻的声音
sounds like this
听起来是这样的
if we want this to just repeat over and
如果我们想让这段话重复一遍
over again we can select this we go to
我们可以再一次选择我们要去的地方
copy or control C on the keyboard and
复制或控制键盘上的C键 然后
then we can just click right before it
然后我们就可以在它前面点击
can go ctrl V to paste click ctrl V
可以按Ctrl V键粘贴 点击Ctrl V键
click ctrl V now we're going to play
点击Ctrl V 现在我们要播放
this section four times in a row so go
这一节连续四次 所以去吧
ahead and play with some of those I
继续和我其中的一些人一起玩
think you're kind of getting the idea I
我觉得你有点理解我的意思了
hope so we can select and we can cut we
希望我们可以选择 我们可以削减我们
can select something and we can copy it
可以选择某个内容 我们可以复制它
at any point if we just click we can
在任何时候 只要我们点击 我们就可以
paste and if we select anything within
粘贴 如果我们选择其中任何内容
our selection when we go to paste
当我们去粘贴的时候我们的选择
we'll get deleted basically and then the
我们基本上会被删除 然后
part that we want to paste will paste
我们要粘贴的部分将被粘贴
overtop of all this so now that's gone
在这一切之上 所以现在这些都消失了
and this is pasted here instead so play
而这是粘贴在这里的 所以播放
with that one more thing I want to show
还有一件事我想展示给大家看
you if we just want to keep a certain
如果我们只是想要保持一定的
part of the song if we only wanted to
歌曲的一部分 如果我们只想
keep like this section right here this
就像这一段就是这一段
short little piece we just want that
很短的一小块 我们只是想要那个
sound we want everything else to be gone
听起来我们希望其他的一切都消失
there's an icon right here we can click
这里有一个图标 我们可以点击
on i'm just called trim audio outside of
我只是在外面被称为Trim Audio
selection if we click this everything
如果我们单击此全部内容 则选择
after it goes away everything before
在它离开之前的一切之后
goes away and we just have this the only
一去不复返 我们只有这一次
issue was doing this is it maintains the
问题是这样做是因为它维护了
that portion of the song that it's apps
歌曲中的应用程序部分
or the timing so this is being played at
或者是时间 所以这是在玩
about eleven and a half seconds in so
大约在11秒半之后
it'll be a bunch of silence if we go
如果我们走了 会是一片寂静
back to the beginning of the composition
回到作文的开头
hit play we should have all the silence
打得好 我们应该保持沉默
forever until it gets to over here so to
直到它到了这里 所以
change that we could actually use our
改变我们实际上可以使用我们的
time shift tools like we've learned and
时移工具 就像我们学到的
we can come over here while time shift
我们可以在时间转换时到这里来
is selected
已选中
left click on it and move it back to the
左键单击它并将其移回
beginning where we want it to be and now
从我们想要的地方开始 现在
when we go to the beginning of the audio
当我们进入音频的开头时
and play go play properly otherwise if
如果不是这样 那就好好玩吧
it was over here it'd be fine
它在这里 会很好的
but when we go to file and export and
但当我们提交文件和出口时
save it the the listener or wherever we
将其保存在监听程序或我们的任何位置
use this it'll have a bunch of empty
用这个它会有一堆空的
space at the beginning which is not
开头的空格不是
usually ideal for audio I think we're
通常是音频的理想选择我认为我们是
gonna end this tutorial here go ahead
本教程将在此处结束 请继续
and play with cut copy and paste just
然后玩剪切、复制和粘贴
know that you can also do
要知道你也可以做到
under the Edit section you can always
在编辑部分下 您始终可以
cut there so if we select I'm sure your
切开那里 如果我们选择 我相信你的
selection tool is selected we can go
选择工具被选中 我们可以去
edit cut and then we can go edit paste
编辑剪切 然后我们可以去编辑粘贴
so there's three ways to do it really
所以有三种方法
the icons here using the edit menu then
这里的图标使用编辑菜单
also the shortcut keys control X control
还有快捷键控制X控制
V to paste and ctrl C to copy I'm just
用V来粘贴 用C来复制 我只是
hitting ctrl V over and over again to
一遍又一遍地击中ckmv
paste all these different sections I
粘贴所有这些不同的部分
hope you found this video informative
希望你能找到这个视频
please like comment subscribe if you
请喜欢评论订阅如果你
have and I hope to see you on the next
我希望下次再见到你
video
视频